Jaturong Duangchaiyusuk, Team Lead & Senior Web Developer

Email: <u>jaturong.duang@gmail.com</u> Mobile: (+66) 86 906 8319 / (+61) 434 980 338

Nationality: Thai

Gender: Male

Visa: Student Visa (subclass 500)

Github: https://github.com/srankmeng

Website: https://srankmeng.github.io/personal-web

Summary / Profile:

I am a web developer who wants to improve my skill always. I have several experiences with software development. For technical skills such as frontend, backend, automated testing, and AWS services (EC2, S3, Lambda, Cloudfront, etc.). I'm good on the frontend more than the backend but I can do it as well. For other skills, I used to use the Agile process in my projects which have planning, backlogs refinement, daily stand-up, and retrospective. And I can use tools that are related to my tasks. In addition, I supported the team like a review code, coaching team members, and finding solutions when having some problems with delivering tasks on time for team success.

Currently:

I am overseas to study English in Brisbane, Australia for 6 months (August to January from Monday to Friday 8.00 AM - 2.00 PM.) So I am looking for a part-time job after the classes. Please feel free to contact me, thank you all.

Experience:

May 2021 - Jul 2022

Team Lead Developer, Redlamp Co., Ltd.

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & clear issue block for delivering the project on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Nest js for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Use Cypress for E2E to automate part
- Delivery website https://app.aday.works includes a back-office site
- Implement API of the mobile application both of IOS and Android

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Senior Backend Developer, SCB

Bangkok, Thailand

- Join in Robinhood application team
- Develop API in OTA feature (online travel agency), connect 3rd party API
- Maintain existing feature
- Use AWS service for support the feature
- Develop the unit test for support the feature

Meeting and discussing with the team

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021

Team Lead Developer, SCG

Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery projects on time.
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use Nuxt js, Flask for web development
- Use Docker and AWS for deployment including setup Github action for CI/CD part
- Delivery website https://www.scg-id.com includes a back-office site

Jan 2017 - Dec 2019

Frontend Team Lead & Senior Developer, Lqid 360 Bangkok, Thailand

- Communicate with any team for clarified the requirement
- Planning & resource management for the delivery projects on time
- Manage source code & versioning
- Review code & coaching team member
- Use React, and Redux for frontend web development
- Motivation team members and making teamwork
- Use jest for unit test
- Discussing with the backend team for design response API
- Delivery of KYC's back-office
- Delivery chat system use in back-office with WebRTC technology
- Delivery monitoring system display with chart

May 2012 - Dec 2016

Frontend Developer

Bangkok, Thailand

- Created HTML & CSS related to designs
- Use jquery to manage data on the frontend side
- Use Angularis v1 to manage data on the frontend side
- Integrate API and display data
- Delivery BigC check QC back-office
- Delivery E-commerce web
- Support team & issues

Educations:

May 2008 - Apr 2012

Computer Engineering Bachelor's Degree

Bangkok, Thailand

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang (KMITL)

Skills: Javascript Expert Jest Skillful

Vue, Nuxt Expert Docker Experienced

Languages:	Thai	Native	English	good command
	Liff	Skillful	Firebase	Skillful
	Python	Skillful	Git	Expert
	Typescript	Experienced	Cypress	Skillful
	Nest js, Node js	Experienced	PostgresSQL & MySQL	Skillful
	Bootstrap	Expert	MongoDB	Skillful
	Jquery	Expert	Odoo	Skillful
	Html & Css	Expert	Agile	Experienced
	React Native	Skillful	Github Action	Skillful
	React, Redux	Experienced	AWS	Skillful

Hobbies:

Cinema, Japanese manga, Watching football, Beer